Guide to the Records of the North American Jewish Students Appeal, undated, 1962, 1964-1996 (bulk 1971-1995) *I-338 and *I-338A
Center for Jewish History, Publisher.
- Series VII: Publications and Printed Matter, undated, 1969, 1971-2005; Box 99-109.
  - Subseries 2: Beneficiaries: Journals, Newsletters, Newspapers, and Printed Matter, undated, 1969, 1973-1995, 2003-2005; Boxes 101, 102, 102a, 103, 104 (Folders 1-3), 106, 107, 107a, 107b, 107c (Folders 1 and 2), 108 (Folders 1-8).
    - Part A: Journals, Newsletters (Subseries 2: Beneficiaries)
      - Prospect(University of Michigan), March-April 1988, September-October 1988, November-December 1988, January-Feburary 1989, September 1990, April-May 1993 (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - Ra'Ashan(Noisemaker) (Vassar College), Spring 1994 (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - Shmate: A Journal of Progressive Jewish Thought, Januayr 1982, June-July 1982, April 1983, Summer 1983 (Box 103, Folder 8)
      - Spirit, The-Ha Ruach(SUNY-Albany), Sep 1978, Oct 1979, Nov 1979, Feb 1980, May 1980, Oct 1980, Dec 1980, Mar 1981, Dec 1981, Oct 1982, Dec 1982, Mar 1983, May 1983, Nov 1983, Fall 1991, Spring-Summer 1992, Winter 1992 (Box 103, Folder 9)
      - Talmedi Chaverim(Reconstructionist Rabbinical College, Philadelphia, PA), June 3, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 10)
      - Urim v'Turim(Yale University), Winter 1986, Fall 1987, Winter 1989, Fall 1993 (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - Yachad News(Penn State Friends of Israel), undated, [1988] (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - Yavneh: A Student Journal for the New Visions of the Jewish Experience(University of Oregon), 1992, 1993, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Part B: Newspapers (Subseries 2: Beneficiaries)
      - American Jewish Ledger-Special Holocaust Museum Supplement, undated (Box 106)
      - B'rashet(New Jewish Media Project) Catalog/Poster (see Series VIII: Ephemera and Poster:Subseries 2: Folder 4: Posters, Beneficiaries and Others), 1973 (Box 106)
      - B'Yachad(California State University, Northridge), December 1980 (Box 106)
      - Challenge(University of Florida, Gainsville), November-December 1979, May-June 1980, Fall 1980, Spring 1981 (Box 106)
      - Genesis(Madison, WI), Apr. 11, 1984; Apr 21, 1986; March 9, 1987; Spring 1988; Fall 1991; Spring 1993 (Box 106)
      - Genesis 2: An Independent Voice for Jewish Renewal(Boston, MA), Various Issues (See Box 104 for later dates, 1986-1989), February 13, 1970 (Vol. 1, No. 1)-May 1980 (Box 106)
      - Change of Location Forms (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - Genesis 2: An Independent Voice for Jewish Renewal(Boston, MA), Various Issues (See Box 104 for later dates, 1986-1989), Sep/Oct 1980-May/Jun 1985 (Box 107)
      - Ha'Am(Michigan State University), October 1976, November 1976 (Box 107)
      - Ha'Am(University of California - Los Angeles), Various Issues, 1976-1977 (Box 107)
      - Change of Location Forms (Box 107a, Folder 1)
      - Ha'Am(University of California - Los Angeles), Various Issues, 1980-1993 (Box 107a)
      - Ha'Etgar(University of California - Berkeley), Various Issues, 1978-1986 (Box 107a)
      - Hagefen(George Washington University), Aviv 5751 [1990] (Box 107a)
      - Ha-Kol (Syracuse U. Hillel), November 1992 (Box 107a)
      - Hamakkor(Wesleyan University)(See Box 102 for later dates), Feb. 1980, Mar 1980, May 1980, Nov. 1980, Nov. 1981, Dec. 1981, Mar. 1983 (Box 107a)
      - Images and The Scribe(University of Toronto), Various Issues and correspondence, 1980-1984 (Box 107a)
      - Images and The Scribe(University of Toronto), Various Issues and correspondence, 1984-1985, 1992-1994 (Box 107b, Folder 1)
      - Jewish Student News(University of Florida), 1989-1993 (Box 107b, Folder 2)
      - Koach(SUNY-Binghamton), January 1991, February 1991 (Box 107b, Folder 2)
      - Koleinu(University of California-Davis), October 1993, November 1993, February 1994 (Box 107b, Folder 2)
      - Leviathan(University of California-Santa Cruz), Various Issues, 1972-1978 (Box 107b, Folder 3)
      - Leviathan(University of California-Santa Cruz), Various Issues, 1978-1987 (Box 107b, Folder 4)
      - Leviathan(University of California-Santa Cruz), Various Issues (See box 102 folder 20 for a Spring 2005 issue), 2003-2004 (Box 107b, Folder 5)
      - Mitzpeh(University of Maryland, College Park), Various Issues, 1984-1990 (Box 107b, Folder 5)
      - News Record(University of Cincinnati), February 13, 1989 (Box 107c, Folder 1)
      - Philadelphia Prism, April 1983, December 1986 (Box 107c, Folder 1)
      - Pillar(SUNY-Oneonta, NY), April 1982, Dec. 1982 (Box 107c, Folder 1)
      - Scout(Bradley University), April 1995 (Box 107c, Folder 1)
      - Shelanu(SUNY-Stony Brook, NY), October 1992, February 1993, October 1993 (Box 107c, Folder 1)
      - Shining Star(SUNY-Stony Brook, NY), Various Issues, 1980-1984 (Box 107c, Folder 1)
      - Shofar: The Five College Jewish Newsmagazine(MA), Various Issues, 1982-1988 (Box 107c)
      - Tagar/Masada Zionist Press(UW Milwaukee), Spring 1992, Winter 1992 (Box 107c, Folder 2)
      - Trident, The(Washington and Lee University), May 5, 1993, May 19, 1993, May 26, 1993 (Box 107c, Folder 2)
    - Part C: Printed Matter (Subseries 2: Beneficiaries)
      - "Confronting the Challenge" and "Chanukah," T'Chiya Publications, [1974-1975] (Box 108, Folder 1)
      - Dirshu Printed Matter, [1975-1976] (Box 108, Folder 2)
      - "Jewish Dietary Laws" and "Shabbat Sourcebook," Dirshu Publications, undated, [1975] (Box 108, Folder 3)
      - "How-to-Book: Starting a Jewish Students Week," by Jonathon Snyder and Lara Fein, Project Chai, 1990 (Box 108, Folder 4)
      - "How to Fight Anti-Semitism: A Student's Proposal," Columbia University, [1991-1992] (Box 108, Folder 5)
      - Jewish Student Handbook, University of Maryland, College Park, 1991-1992 (Box 108, Folder 6)
      - Laza Youth Group, "Springs of Jewish Wisdom" and Pamphlet, undated, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 7)
      - Southwest Jewish Conference "Two Images, One Destiny" by Elie Wiesel and "The Arab League: Who's Threatening Who?" ADL Card, circa 1975 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 3: Other Organizations: Journals, Newsletters, Newspapers, and Publications, undated, 1971-1995; Boxes 104 (Folders 4-24), 104a, 104b, 107c (Folders 3 and 4), 107e, 108 (Folders 9-26), and 109.
    Box 104, 104a, and 104b contain journals and magazines.Box 107c, 107d, and 107e contain newspaper format materials.Box 108 (Folders 9-26) and Box 109 contains printed matter including articles, guides, programs, handbooks, and proceedings.
    Subseries 3: Other Organizations represents publications and printed matter derived from national, professional, and student organizations that were not Constituents or Beneficiaries of the APPEAL. Primarily the materials were collected through the everyday running of the APPEAL, or sent to the APPEAL by the organization for information purposes.Boxes 104, 104a, and 104b contain journals and magazines from national Jewish student organizations (Hillel, UJA, etc.), groups that represented issues such as Ethiopian or Turkish Jews, publications from the Israeli consulate and AIPAC, and one copy of the newsmagazine The Nation, which carried a March 1988 article on the state of student movements.Boxes 107c, 107d, and 107e contains newspaper format materials, mostly deriving from non-beneficiary student groups, though the box also contains the international edition of the Jerusalem Post with a 40thanniversary supplement of the Palestine Post; a newsletter entitled Shofar from the 'jubilee' community of Tempe, AR, and a Fall 1992 edition of Voice of the Trees, a publication devoted to Jewish participation in environmental issues.Box 108 (Folders 9-26) and Box 109 contains printed matter including articles, guides, programs, handbooks, and proceedings surrounding Jewish-related themes such as anti-Semitism on campus, intermarriage, student radicalism and activism, trends in American Jewish population and Jewish community. Of note is a history of Breira, an organization concerned with U.S. Jewish Diaspora and Israeli relations over issues surrounding the Israeli/Arab conflict. (See Box 24, Folder 2 for more information.)
    - Part A: Journals, Newsletters (Subseries 3: Other Organizations)
      - A.A.J.F.T. Newsletter(American Association of Jewish Friends of Turkey), January-Feburary 1993 (Box 104, Folder 4)
      - AIPAC on Campus, October 19, 1987, March 21, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - Book Peddler: Newsletter of the National Yiddish Book, Fall 1981, Summer 1985 (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - Camera on Campus: The Committee for Accuracy in Middle East Reporting in America, Fall 1992, Spring 1993 (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - Campus Connection(B'Nai B'Rith Hillel), undated, February 1991, October 1991, February 1992, November 1992, Year End 1992, Spring 1993, Winter 1993, 1993-1994, Spring 1994 (Box 104, Folder 8)
      - Campus Review(Journal of the Student Representatives of the USD/ American Zionist Youth Foundation-The Israel Action Center), August 1992, November-December 1992, April-May 1993 (Box 104, Folder 9)
      - Capital Report(CJF-Washington Action Office), November 1992 (Box 104, Folder 10)
      - Congress Bi-Weekly: A Journal of Opinion and Jewish, November 12, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 11)
      - Dialogue(Dor Hamshech-Young Jewish Leadership), vol. I no. 7, vol. II no. 1, vol. II no. 2, undated, [1970s] (Box 104, Folder 12)
      - Erensia Sefardi Newsletter, Winter 1993 (Box 104, Folder 13)
      - Flame, The (Chadash/New Light), September-October 1981, February-March 1982 (Box 104, Folder 14)
      - Genesis 2: An Independent Voice for Jewish Renewal, Mailers, no date, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 15)
      - Genesis 2: An Independent Voice for Jewish Renewal, various issues.(See Boxes 106 and 107 for earlier issues), Feb/Mar 1986-Autumn 1987 (Box 104, Folder 16)
      - Genesis 2: An Independent Voice for Jewish Renewal, various issues.(See Boxes 106 and 107 for earlier issues), Winter 1987/88-Autumn 1989 (Box 104, Folder 17)
      - Havurah!(The Newsletter of the National Havurah Committee), Autumn 1993 (Box 104, Folder 18)
      - Hillel Gazette, February 1992 (Box 104, Folder 19)
      - Igeret(Newsletter of the B'Nai B'rith Hillel-International Center), April 1988, September 1988, November 1988, December 1988, February 1989, March 1989, April 1989, June 1989, September 1989, November 1989, December 1989, February 1980, September 1980, February 1991, March 1991, December 1992, March 1993, May 1993, September 1993, December 1993, February 1994 (Box 104, Folder 20)
      - Israel Horizons: The Socialist Zionist Journal, April-May 1991 (Box 104, Folder 21)
      - Koach on Campus(United Synagogue of Conservative Judaism), Autumn 1992, Winter 1992 (Box 104, Folder 22)
      - Lights(Jewish Association for College Youth-JACY), undated [Winter 1984], Spring 1984 (Box 104, Folder 23)
      - Monitor!: Digest of News and Analysis from Soviet Successor States, April 1992, December 1992, May 1993 (Box 104, Folder 24)
      - Nation, The, Students on the Move Issue, March 26, 1988 (Box 104a, Folder 1)
      - News and Views(World Jewish Congress-WJS), January-February 1989 (Box 104a, Folder 2)
      - Reflections(National Jewish Center for Learning and Leadership), February 1992 (Box 104a, Folder 3)
      - Release: A Report of the American Association of Ethiopian Jewry(AAEJ), Fall 1983 (Box 104a, Folder 4)
      - Sh'ma: A Journal of Jewish Responsibility(UJA/University Student Program), April 30, 1993 (Box 104a, Folder 5)
      - Star of David, May 1987 (Box 104a, Folder 6)
      - Tarbut: Israeli Cultural Affairs in North America, Fall 1992, Winter 1993 (Box 104a, Folder 7)
      - UJA-Young Leadership Cabinet Communique, Special Washington Conference Edition, Spring 1990 (Box 104a, Folder 8)
      - Youth and Nation(Hashomer Hatzair), various issues, 1941-1942 (Box 104a, Folder 9)
      - Youth and Nation(Hashomer Hatzair), various issues, 1943-1944 (Box 104a, Folder 10)
      - Youth and Nation(Hashomer Hatzair), various issues, 1945-1946 (Box 104a, Folder 11)
      - Youth and Nation(Hashomer Hatzair), various issues, 1947-1948 (Box 104a, Folder 12)
      - Youth and Nation(Hashomer Hatzair), various issues, 1949-1950 (Box 104b, Folder 1)
      - Youth and Nation(Hashomer Hatzair), various issues, 1951-1952 (Box 104b, Folder 2)
      - Youth and Nation(Hashomer Hatzair), various issues, 1968-1971 (Box 104b, Folder 3)
      - Youth and Nation(Hashomer Hatzair), various issues, 1972-1975 (Box 104b, Folder 4)
      - Youth and Nation(Hashomer Hatzair), various issues, 1976-1978 (Box 104b, Folder 5)
      - Youth and Nation(Hashomer Hatzair), various issues, 1979-1981 (Box 104b, Folder 6)
    - Part B: Newspapers (Subseries 3: Other Organizations)
      - Forum: The Jewish Student Publications at NYU(New York University), Mar. 1980, May 1980, Dec. 1980, Mar. 1981, Dec. 1981, Feb. 1982, Apr. 1982, Mar. 1983, Oct. 1983, May 1984, Sep. 1984, Nov. 1984, Dec. 1984, Mar. 1985, Apr. 1985, Sep. 1985, Nov. 1985, Nov/Dec. 1985, Jan/Feb. 1986, Mar. 1986, Sep. 1986, Apr. 1987. (Box 107c, Folder 3)
      - Frontier(Columbia, MO), February 1991 (Box 107c, Folder 4)
      - Ha-Or(Queens College), Various Issues, 1972-1973 (Box 107c, Folder 4)
      - Ha-Or(Queens College), Various Issues, 1973-1976 (Box 107d, Folder 1)
      - Ha-Or(Queens College), Various Issues, 1976-1978 (Box 107d, Folder 2)
      - Ha-Or(Queens College), Various Issues, 1978-1981 (Box 107d, Folder 3)
      - Ha-Or(Queens College), Various Issues, 1981-1984 (Box 107e, Folder 1)
      - Hatikvah-The Hope(Brooklyn College), March 1980, January 1982 (Box 107e, Folder 1)
      - Jerusalem Post(International Edition) and The Palestine Post(40th Anniversery Edition of the Jerusalem Post), 1982, 1988 (Box 107e, Folder 2)
      - Jewish Women's Journal, February 1993 (Box 107e, Folder 2)
      - L'Chayim(University of California-San Diego), Various Issues, 1981-1987 (Box 107e, Folder 3)
      - New Torch and The Torch(New York University), Various Issues (See Box 111 folder 9 for other issues), 1987-1979 (Box 107e, Folder 3)
      - Observer(Stern College for Women, Yeshiva University), Various Issues, 1968-1980 (Box 107e, Folder 3)
      - Shofar: A Newsletter from Jubilee Community(Tempe, AR), [1973] (Box 107e, Folder 3)
      - Voice of the Trees(Shomrei Adamah), Fall 1992 (Box 107e, Folder 3)
    - Part C: Printed Matter (Subseries 3: Other Organizations)
      - Academy and Community: A Study of the Jewish Identity and Involvement of Professors by Albert G. Crawford and Rela Geffin Monson, pgs. 23-37 Excerpt, undated (Box 108, Folder 9)
      - American Jewish Committee (AJC) Publications Brochure, undated (Box 108, Folder 10)
      - Anti-Semitism on the Campus: A Report of the National Jewish Relations Advisory Council, November 1990 (Box 108, Folder 11)
      - Avi Chai Foundation Brochure and "First Five Years", undated, June 1990 (Box 108, Folder 12)
      - "Blowing in the Wind: Jewish Radicals" by Sherman Rosenfeld,Davka, Winter 1974 (Box 108, Folder 13)
      - Breira: Counsel for Justice by Rael Jean Issac/Jewish Week Controversy, [1977] (Box 108, Folder 14)
      - "Building and Awareness of a Continental Jewish Community," North American Jewish Data Bank Occasional, May 1987 (Box 108, Folder 15)
      - California Community Foundation Report for Fiscal Year, 1977 (Box 108, Folder 16)
      - "Food: A Yiddish Terminology" by Mordkhe Schaecter, 1976 (Box 108, Folder 17)
      - Foundations Annual Reports and Brochures, undated, 1991 (Box 108, Folder 18)
      - "Guide to Jewish Student Activism," Draft 1.0 by Lana Becker, Moshe Schwartz and Rob Slater, 1990 (Box 108, Folder 19)
      - "Guidelines for the Development of College and Youth Faculty Programs," CJF Committee on College Youth and, December 1992 (Box 108, Folder 20)
      - "Highlights from the Guttman Institute Report: Beliefs, Observations and Social Interaction Among Israeli Jews," Avi Chai Foundation, December 1993 (Box 108, Folder 21)
      - Hillel Jewish Student Center, Rose Warner House, Fall Arts Festival Program, November 1987 (Box 108, Folder 22)
      - Hillel Reports and Publications; Intermarriage Symposium Proceedings and Publication (See Box 22, Folder 9), 1990-1992 (Box 108, Folder 23)
      - International Arid Lands Consortium (Jewish National Fund), undated, 1991 (Box 108, Folder 24)
      - "Jewish Involvement of the Baby Boom Generation," Executive Summary by the Avi Chai Foundation, November 1993 (Box 108, Folder 25)
      - "Jewish Women's Call for Peace: A Handbook for Jewish Women on the Israeli/Palestinian Conflict," Rita Falbel, Irena Klepfisz and Donna Nevel, eds., 1990 (Box 108, Folder 26)
      - "Multiculturalism: Rhetoric and Reality," Ruth Fredman Cernea, ed., 1993 (Box 109, Folder 1)
      - Proceedings of Breira's First Annual Membership, 1977 (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - Rabbinical Assembly Membership List, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 3)
      - Student Coalition for Soviet Jewry (SCSJ) Congressional Handbook, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 4)
      - "Toward an American Jewish Culture: New Perspectives on Jewish Continuity," National Foundation for Jewish, undated, [1994] (Box 109, Folder 5)
      - Union of American Hebrew Congregations (UAHC) College Action Series Guides, [1993] (Box 109, Folder 6)
      - United Synagogue of Conservative Judaism Department of College Outreach/KOACH Outreach Guides, 1990s (Box 109, Folder 7)
      - "When Hate Comes to Town: A College Students Guide to Countering Extremism," Anti-Defamation League (ADL), 1988 (Box 109, Folder 8)
      - "Where Do Our Dollars Go?" Jewish Agency Reprinted, 1986 (Box 109, Folder 9)
      - World Union of Jewish Students (WUJS) Institute Sample Catalogue Jewish/Israel Studies Programme Hebrew Language Ulplan and Flyer, circa 1979 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- Series VIII: Ephemera and Posters, undated, 1971-1995; Box 110-111.
  Series VIII is divided into two Subseries, one containing ephemera and one containing posters.
  The series primarily highlights the promotional materials which derived from the NAJSA, its Constituents and Beneficiaries as well as items created by national and student Jewish organizations for the benefit of self-promotion and the conveying of ideas associated with the Jewish community.
  - Subseries 1: Ephemera, undated, 1973-1995; Box 110-111 (Folders 1-3).
    Arranged in no particular order. Box 111 is located in OS 1. Box 110 is shared with Series X.
    Subseries 1 holds buttons, stickers, from various organizations including the NAJSA and its Constituents SSSJ, YUGNTRUF and NETWORK. Of special interest is a button produced by YUGNTRUF (in Yiddish) that says "Speak Yiddish with Me" and a NETWORK sticker created in response to the Yom Kippur War highlighting an Israel information hotline. SSSJ's ephemera include a "Free Soviet Jews" button and "Save Soviet Jewry" bumper sticker. Items from Beneficiaries are also included. Among these items are a 1995 Stanford University Jewish Gay and Lesbian symposium (Box 61, Folder 12) key chain and t-shirt that can be found in Box 110, Folder 7, Box 111, Folder 3, a University of Michigan Hebrew bumper sticker and a GIPAC Soviet Jewry Week button.
    - "I'm a Friend of the Students" North American Jewish Students APPEAL Button, undated (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - "Israel Must Live Israel Will Live Am Israel Chai" Sticker, [October 1973] (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - "NETWORK: Israel Control Central for Israel Information Hotline" Sticker, [October 1973] (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - "Free Soviet Jews" SSSJ Button, circa 1970s (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - "Speak Yiddish to Me" Yugntruf Buttons, undated (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - "GIPAC Soviet Jewry Week, 1988; Today is My Day to Fast for Soviet Jewry" Button (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - "Members of the Tribe" Stanford University Keychain, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - "Be Proud Be Jewish" LAZA Youth Button, circa 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - University of Michigan Hebrew Bumper Sticker, [1988-1989] (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - "Student Struggle for American Jewry" Sticker Buttons, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - "We Are the Next Generation" NAJSA Ribbon Buttons, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Ribbon Sets for Campaign to Support Isreal During Gulf War, Syracuse University, [1991] (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Hillel Conference Bookmark, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - "Save Soviet Jewry" SSSJ Bumper Sticker, circa 1970s (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - "Jewish Students Have APPEAL!" NAJSA Stickers, undated (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - "Members of the Tribe" Stanford University T-Shirt, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 2: Posters, undated, 1973-1995; Box 111 (Folders 4-8).
    Arranged in informal subseries by specific Constituent,Beneficiary Grants, and Others.
    Subseries 2 holds posters in various sizes from the NAJSA, its Constituents and Beneficiaries as well as other national and campus-based Jewish organizations.
    - JSPS/NETWORK/RESPONSE, undated; 1973,; [1982],; 1991
      - "International General Assembly of Jewish Students" NETWORK Conference Poster, undated (Box 111, Folder 4)
      - "Multiculturalism, Jews and the Campus: A Symposium" JSPS/RESPONSE Poster (2), 1991 (Box 111, Folder 4)
      - "This is Zionism: From Persecution to Freedom!" NETWORK Poster, undated (Box 111, Folder 4)
      - "We Are the Next Generation" NAJSA Poster, [1982] (Box 111, Folder 4)
      - Yom Kippur War Packet Posters (2), 1973 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Lights in Action, 1990s
      - "Free Love" by Rabbi Avraham Yitzchak HaCohen Cook Poster, [1990s] (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - "A Guide for the Perplexed" Poster (2), [1993] (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - Israel Tours Poster, [1993?] (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - Poster Calendar, 1992-1993, 1994-1995 (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - Shabbat Leumit/Shabbat for the People Card, [1990s] (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - SSSJ
      - "Arabs Conquer Israel" Poster, circa 1971-1974 (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - "Freedom Ride for Alexei Magarik: The Youngest Prisoner of Zion" Poster, [1986] (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - "In America, You Have to Kill Someone to Get 12 Years in Prison. In Russia, You May Just Have to Teach Hebrew" Poster, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - "Kruschev, 1903-1971: From Pogroms to Prison Camps" Poster, circa 1971 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Beneficiary Grants
      - Chai Week at Yale University Posters (2), 1990 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - Elie Wiesel's Trial of God at Washington University Production Poster, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - "Witnessing the Holocaust" Dr. Leon Bass Lecture at Bradley University Poster, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - Holocaust Memorial Week at Brandeis Poster, 119 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - Holocaust Memorial Day Viewing of Europa, Europa at California State, Long Beach, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - James L. Young Lectures on Holocaust Memory and Memorials at the University of Virginia Hillel, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - LAZA Membership Flyer, [1975-1976] (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - "A New Generation of Women: Weaving Our Tapestry" at Hillel of Greater Boston, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - Holocaust Remembrance Week Georgia Tech/Atlanta Young Jewish Adult (YAD) Agency Posters, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - Meir Michel Abehsera Posters (4), [1975-1976] (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - Middle East Policy Lecture by Jonathon Kessler at University of Wisconsin, [1992] (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - 10th Anniversary of the Camp David Accords Commemoration at the University of Illinois, 1989 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - "Drink Coca-Cola" LAZA Campaign Against Pepsi Hebrew Poster, circa 1976 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - "The First Catalog" (Poster/Publication) New Jewish Media Project, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 7)
      - 14th Annual Conference on the Holocaust at University of Michigan, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 7)